vipbrands.az 2014-06-06

# Privacy - Vipbrands AZ

### Privacy Agreement

This decleration includes privacy policy of ****VipBrands.com**. When you visit **VipBrands.com** website, we will agree that you accept the conditions and rules.**

 **

**VipBrands.com** demands some personal information during registration and after. Protecting these personal information and maintaining privacy is the main priority of **VipBrands.com**. Therefore, none of your personal information will be used besides the purposes of the user agreement and will not be shared third parties.

**VipBrands.com** determines and applies users' IP adresses if needed to determine and solve the system problems in a fastest way. IP adress is also necessary to define the users in general and to collect detailed demographic information. 

VipBrands is demanding some of your personal information such as your name, age, interests, e-mail address to serve better to you. 

The information collected in VipBrands servers are used for categorize our customers by doing periodic event studies, speculating special event activities intended for customer profiles and not sending the undesirable e-mails to customers only by VipBrands. 

Our customers' personal information we collected at registration forms will not be definitely shared third parties. Those information will not be used for any trade goal or will not be sold. 

The statistical information which doesn't include our customers' personal information can be shared with our business partners to serve more special and effective shopping experience for our customers. 

Customer data may be disclosed to the authorities at their request, in case you must perform whatever legal obligations. Personal data, specified by a client, are only available to the client and can be change only by the client. Access to these data and changing them by a third party is impossible. 

If you want to quit from the VipBrands emailing list, you can easily quit by clicking on **please click here to quit E-bulletin**. Your credit card information has not been reserved by neither our servers nor the companies we work with to provide the best sequrity for our customers. 

With our 128-bit SSL certificate your personal data are fully protected with coding from access of third parties. 

The system demands contact information for instance: name, surname, e-mail address, phone number, address for application forms, order forms, questionnaires and contests. Moreover, system demands credit card information during shopping. These personal information is needed to receive the orders, to offer our products and services, to carry out your payments, to make your orders reach to you, to inform you about your orders, to contact for marketing our products and services, to update your personal information, to magane your membership and maintain, to recommend the products and services may interest you, to make third parties provide technical, logistics functions. 

After being a member of **VipBrands.com** , e-mails for informing our members will be sent daily, weekly. Our members can give up, change or restart this service anytime they wish. The contents of these e-mails are the new products you may like, the adds of third parties etc. The demographic information is used for adapting our website depending on our customers' interests. These informations can be shared with the advertising companies to adapt the adds for the target group. During this process none of your personal information will be shared, they are only used to conclude about the user tendencies and used for segmentation. The financial infos are collecting to invoice your orders. During shopping we need your financial infos and share them with 3. parties like banks and credit card companies to operate the shopping process. The financial information to share are credit card number, its expiration date, its CVV2 number and other infos needed. 

Our customers' credit card and personal informations are codified by SSL secure system that is the standard of security. By this way, our customers' personal or credit card information cannot be captured by any institution or a person. You can e-mail us to ask or to recommend about our security system. 

The process of cancelling **VipBrands.com** membership can be carried out by e-mailing destek@vipbrands.com or you can follow 'Cancelling Membership' under 'My Account' at **VipBrands.com**.

You can reach us via 

destek@vipbrands.com or 

012 4803323 for any question.

**
